http://www.anitabell.com/privacy

Effective Date: May 1, 2007
Tarampa-Studios values the users of our website www.anitabell.com (the "Website"). Your privacy and trust are very important to us. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we collect when you use the Website and the services offered on the Website ("Tarampa-Studios Services"). This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Our policy and security is authorised and managed by deconetwork.com
Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers and Online Partners. We will only disclose your information to relevant third party service providers and online partners; The Print Bar to print and send our product/s and to Pay Pal who accepts our payments.
If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at bleetie@bigpond.com.
Does Tarampa-Studios Ever Make Changes to its Privacy Policy?
We may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by sending you an email, posting a notice on the home page of the Website, or posting a notice in your account when you first login after we have made changes. If you receive notification of a change in our Privacy Policy, you must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures. You may not be able to receive notices from us if your cookies are not set to accept and/or are disabled.
What Types of Information Does Tarampa-Studios Collect?
Personal Information. We collect Personal Information that you provide to us, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card number, and financial information. Non-Personal Information. We also collect non-personal information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your Internet protocol (IP) Address Non-Personal Information cannot be easily used to personally identify you.
How and When Does Tarampa-Studios Collect This Information?
Providing Information to Us. We collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you purchase a product sold through an affiliate, we may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, and email address. If you create an account, we may collect your name, tax identification number, mailing address, email address, and other information that we request during the registration process, and any information that you provide to Tarampa-Studios. If you sign up to receive a newsletter, we will collect your email address. Communications With Us. If you communicate with us regarding the Website or the System, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication. Analytic and Reporting Technologies. Like the operators of most websites, we use analytic and reporting technologies to record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software, operating system types, click stream patterns, and the dates and times that the Website and the System are accessed. We also contract with several online partners to help manage, monitor and optimise our Website and the System and to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, communications and how visitors use the Website. To do this, we may use web beacons and cookies.
How Does Tarampa-Studios Use My Information?
Personal Information. We use Personal Information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the Website, fulfilling requests for information, producing and shipping the products that you order, and providing customer support. For example, if you create an Account, we will use the information that you provide us to communicate with you and pay you any commissions that you earn. Similarly, if you sign up to receive a Tarampa-Studios newsletter, we will use the email address you provide to send you the newsletters. Non-Personal Information. We use Non-Personal Information to track the use of the Website and the System and for other internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the Website.
When Will Tarampa-Studios Disclose My Information to Third Parties?
Disclosure to Successors. We will not disclose Personal Information to any other company.
Disclosure to Unaffiliated Third Parties. We will not disclose your Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties.
Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers and Online Partners. We will not disclose your details to various third parties except Pay Pal who accepts our payments.
Disclosure to Affiliates. We do not disclose your details to any of our affiliates execept our couriers.
Disclosure of Non-Personal Information. We will not disclose Non-Personal Information either to any third party.
What About Cookies and Web Beacons?
A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most websites use cookies. We use cookies to track your use of the Website and the System, provide you with a more personalized user experience, and to allow you to login and begin use of the Website automatically when you visit the Website. A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, usually no larger than a 1x1 pixel that is placed on a web page or in an e-mail that is used to monitor the behaviour of the user visiting the Website or receiving the e-mail. Cookies and web beacons used by Tarampa-Studios and our online partners are not linked to Personal Information. Some of our Shopkeepers may use cookies or web beacons on our Website. We have no access to or control over these cookies and web beacons. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies and web beacons by Tarampa-Studios and our online partners only and does not cover the use of cookies or web beacons by any other third party.
Does Tarampa-Studios Protect My Personal Information?
Personal Information. Whenever we obtain your Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. We have in place strong methods to protect your information but we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control. Website Content. We are not responsible for the actions of others. Therefore, you should use care in communicating with other users and only disclose your Personal Information to other users that you know to be trustworthy. You should not assume that your content will be kept private.
How Can I Review and Make Changes to My Personal Information?
You can obtain a copy of and request that we correct errors in your Personal Information by emailing us at bleetie@bigpond.com. For your protection, you will be required to provide proof of your identity to obtain a copy of your Personal Information. If your Personal Information changes or if you no longer want to use the Tarampa-Studios Services, you may correct, update or deactivate your Personal Information and/or your account through the account management screen. If you would like to deactivate or terminate your account you can also contact our Customer Service.
Tell-A-Friend
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about the Website, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Website. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number and/or social security number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Does This Privacy Policy Apply When I Access Third Party Websites?
You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to its provider.
What About Children's Privacy?
Under Thirteen. The Website and the System are intended for users aged 13 and older only. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children that we know to be under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13. Thirteen to Seventeen. Prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 can only use the Website under their parent's or legal guardian's supervision. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, you, your parent, or your legal guardian may request that we deactivate any of your Personal Information in our database and/or opt-out from receiving communications from us. If you wish to do so, please contact us at bleetie@bigpond.com.
Can I Opt-Out From Receiving Communications From Tarampa-Studios?
We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information used for certain purposes. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at bleetie@bigpond.com. We also offer you an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications through the account management screen. If you need assistance you may contact us at bleetie@bigpond.com. If we disclose your Personal Information to a third party in a manner that is not set forth in this Privacy Policy you will be notified so that you can make an informed choice about sharing your Personal Information with that third party.
Your cart is empty
Close
Home
ON SALE
Designs
About
FAQs
Contact
Currency:
Select Currency
{CC} - {CN}
Cancel
